I was able to put the new Kimi K2 model
into cloud code. It was able to create
this whole high quality UI component
library including file explorer, text
editor, app view, and resizable panels
and put together an online IDE UI like
this as well as a fully functional Mario
type game with just friction of cost of
what you would normally be charged from
entropic API. And I know there are new
models came out all the time, but this
Kimi K2 model is something truly
different. So when it come to AI coding
entropic claude has been the best model
out there. There are not even many other
choice like GBD4.1 models coding
capability is not even come close. But
the issue is that clot 4 model cost is
extremely high. I was trying to build
this coding agent for super design dev
and that's where I couldn't figure out
how possibly we can make using those
entropic model and that's also the point
I realized all those AI coding platform
like lobo or bonu very likely are not
making much profit if their customer are
using the product much but that is going
to be totally changed with this kim K2
model so Kim K2 is a new open source
model introduced by this AI company in
China called moonshot it has quite
impressive coding capabilities on the
benchmarks but most importantly their
price is insanely low compared with
cloud 4 model or even GPD4.1 where cloud
4 charge $3 per million input token and
$15 for output token. The Kim K2 model
charge only a fraction of it with 60
cents for 1 million input token and $2.5
for the output token which means if you
switch to Kimi K2 model you will cut
cost by 80% immediately and I did some
test the performance of Kimi model looks
really promising it almost feel like
somewhere between cloud 3.5 and cloud 4.
So it is good enough but 80% cheaper. So
today I want to show you how can you use
Kimmy model in your own application as
well as cloud code. So there are a few
ways you can experiment the Kimmy K2
model. In this one you can just go to
kimi.com start give a prompt. Here I
just give screenshot Twitter and ask to
review the UI. It will automatically
generate this pretty amazing UI replica.
So you can just go to kim.com to try
out. But on the other side, the more fun
ways to use Kim K2 is obviously using
their API endpoint. And the price, as I
mentioned before, is pretty insanely
cheap. Considering their performance and
the best part is that it's extremely
easy to use their API because you just
change the base URL and passing on API
key. It just work like a normal open AI
client that you create before. But the
best way to experience Kim K2 is
actually integrate that into cloud code
so that it leverage both the coding
capability as well as the agentic to
core capability. And the easiest way to
integrate is that you can just open your
terminal and do export entropic o token
equal to the API key that you got from
moonshot. So you can go to platform.m
moonshot.ai and generate an API key
here. Meanwhile, making sure just top up
some money. You can just top out $10.
That will be enough for you to do a lot
of things with Kim K2's pricing. So you
will do export entropic all token equal
to the moonshot API you got. And also do
export entropic base URL equal to
API.shot.ai/entropic. AI/entropic.
And now if you open cloud code again,
you will see it is calling moonshot API.
And you will also notice that it became
a bit slower than normal because Kim K2
API is a little bit slower than
entropic. Now we can start doing some
experiments. First I want to try out the
UI design capability from Kimi K2 model.
So I just do PMP DRX chassing at latest
initiate to set up a Unex.js project and
name the folder to Kim UI test. Then
I'll get inside Kim UI test runcloud.
And now give a prompt help me build a UI
component for tree structure file
explorer and show that component on the
homepage. And while it is running here
I'm also going to set up a new folder
called uh let's say ki game test. So I
also want to test out how good kimi will
be in term of building like more complex
UI or games produce cd ki game and again
we're going to explore the o token as
well as entropy based URL and just
making sure this overrides message show
up. So here I will give a prompt. Help
me build a simple marrow game for all
game assets you can find online. So I
have two agents working simultaneously.
Cool. So now I can try to run the
project. I open new terminal and pmppm
dev. So it does get some arrows and I
can just copy those arrow paste in.
Cool. So after one round test it's up
running with no arrows and you can see
the UI component create here looks
really good and I can ask it to do a bit
more things as well. also help me build
a UI component for rich text editor. So
the game here is ready for use. I can
open in Finder and just open this. Wow,
it actually create a like functional
marrow game. This is absolutely insane.
And now if I switch back to the UI test,
it got some new error again, but I'm
pretty sure I can just fix it if I paste
in here. Cool. Now we also have this
rich text editor UI component that looks
I would say pretty good and it's fully
functional. I can select some test with
different styles. I can even add a link
here as well. So it's really awesome. I
can even prompt it further to say now
help me think through what other UI
components needed to build an IDE type
of experience. If I go to Moonshot to
check how much does it cost so far to
build those UI components as well as
research to build this marrow game. The
cost so far is less than 10 cents which
is absolutely insane. If I'm using cloud
4, I'm pretty sure it will close to at
least 50 or 60 cents. And heading back,
it come up with list of different
components to build this. And I can just
prompt it to build some core components.
Meanwhile, for the game, I can prompt
the game generators to say add more
detail to the game assets and also make
the map longer and more sophisticated so
players can play longer. Okay, great. So
after the second attempt, it does
generate a fully functional game that
does look like the first run of the
Mario game. And if I switched back to
the IDE component, you can see that here
it actually put together different
components into this pretty awesome IDE
UI where I can click on that and it will
allow me to edit text directly and it
also had terminal at the bottom even
though it's not functional because it's
just a UI component. But hey, the
quality here is actually really amazing.
If I swap back to check the cost to
build this Mario game as well as this
IDE UI components only cost around 50
cents, which is absolutely amazing. I'm
pretty sure if you use cloud, you will
expect somewhere like $2. So here is how
you can use Kim K2 model in your real
world use case. Again, and the part I
feel most exciting is that now we can
build AI coding agent with a very
manageable cost. I think you can totally
do the same thing using cloud code SDK
for your own AI coding agents to cut the
cost by 80% immediately. And if you guys
interested, please comment below. I can
make a tutorial of how to use Kim K2
model with a cloud code SDK. And if
you're interested, you can join next
week's AI builder cloud community call
where we're taking through the best
practice of using cloud code as well as
some more experience and integration
with Kim K2 model into those existing AI
coding ID. I hope you enjoy this video.
Thank you and I see you next